<tile>
	<text>You spend the following days wandering the swamp, meditating and practicing the arcane arts. At first it is impossible for you to obtain any clarity of mind whatsoever, but as the days pass you begin to regain a semblance of inner peace. While Aeturnus may not have saved her when he had the chance, you are forced to face the fact that you gave her no more thought than he did once your training had begun, and Ursala was not defenseless by any stretch of the imagination. There is plenty of blame to go around, and nothing to be gained by dwelling in it. 
It is a difficult decision to return to Aeturnus, but in the end must admit you do not believe he is any more to blame than you are. In addition you have a practical reason for at least a short visit, since that days events your spells have had a distinctly different feel to them. You are not even sure how to describe it, except that they feel more alive somehow. 
The first thing that strikes you upon entering the now familiar clearing is the freshly dug grave standing at the base of a massive tree near the edge of the encroaching wilderness. The bark of the tree has been shaped into her likeness, the living bark captures her beauty better than any painting could. 
"I'm sorry my friend. In my haste and need to defeat evil, I forgot what we were fighting for. I can only beg your forgiveness and for a second chance." Aeturnus gently puts a hand on your shoulder pulling back into the present. 
It is with renewed effort and focus that you delve back into your studies. The wizard reveals to you that in your struggle with the swamp, a certain bond was formed. Much of its ancient power is now available to you, although what effects and applications this will have is unclear, even to Aeturnus. Despite this uncertainty, you find new faith in both your own abilities and in the counsel of your friend. It is with a sense of conviction and confidence that you set off several months later, two wizards beginning a new journey, one that you hope can change the world for the better.

You win! Or do you? Only one way to know, write a sequel.
</text>
	<image>darkswamp.jpg</image>
</tile>