<tile>
	<text>Even blinded by emotion as you are, it is immediately apparent something has changed. The ordeal you just went through should have left you drained and barely able to focus your energies. Magic draws its power from the vitality of your body and soul, and while extreme circumstances can help with concentration no man can exceed the limits of his physical body. And yet you feel even stronger than before. Your first strike is a simple incantation utilizing your strongest element. A large fireball explodes from your fingertips towards your old master, but it seems as if the swamp strikes with you, tendrils of sludge are drawn into the whirling mass and weave through it in thick tendrils. Suddenly a single point of light pokes through the center, with an imperceptible twist it unravels your attack around it then darts towards you. Without thought you swat it away, behind you the trees it touches burst like fireworks, unnoticed by either contestant. Aeturnus shows no hesitation or mercy. A relentless stream of attacks come at you from every direction with no warning or pattern. At first you attempt to counter his attacks in the manner in which he taught you, extinguishing fire with water, dissipating lighting with wind, and so on. 
Seeing your efforts the master wizard increases the frequency and variety of his deadly efforts. For a moment you are almost overcome. Vines of fire spring from the ground circle your feet, a tornado of electricity tears towards you, a million needles of light seem to fall from the sky all pointed directly at your head. From within you feel the same primal energy you felt when battling the swamp, without thought you let it fill you, until it seems you can feel it about to burst through your skin. Unbidden your mouth forms an ancient spell, one older than man, until now known only to the swamp. For a moment Aeturnus is lit up, surrounded by a glowing shield, then the swamp itself seems to rise up and swallow him, his shield shatters and it blotted out by the vicious implosion.
                             ..........
It is many hours later when you finally regain consciousness. All that remains of the wizard is his staff, a small flower already curling around it. You pick it up with a feral smile. Somehow you can feel your former masters hut deep in the swamp, you set off in that direction, already considering several improvements you could make.
</text>
</tile>