<tile>
	<text>After waiting several minutes and several more raps on the door it abruptly jerks open. You are surprised to see the person at the door is both female and dressed in leather pants and a coat. For a moment you are taken aback, is this person the merchants servant or a wife with some eccentricities? After a moments consideration you choose what appears to be the safest option.
"Afternoon ma'am. Is the master of the house home?"
She looks at you with what strikes you as a mixture of annoyance and resignation. "You're talking to her."
For a second you simply stare uncomprehending. The woman regards you icily for a second, "You must be one of those Easterners people are always telling tales about. If you hadn't realized already, around here kidnapping a women will get you a one way trip to the stocks, not a wife. And another thing, I'll have you know we won't be taking or selling any slaves on this trip. If you don't like it you can fuck off." She crosses her arms, gauging your reaction.
After a moments consideration, several things occur to you. First and foremost the fact that you haven't eaten since the previous day, the faint smell of food from the back of the house is enough to make your mouth water. More to the point, although less pressing, half the reason you left The Republic in the first place was what they did to…you shake your head, bringing yourself back to the present. You give a short bow, "Ma'am merchant, I would feel privileged to have the honor of guarding your wares. And I would never own a slave."
For a second she merely stares at you, then breaks the silence with a small smile, "Glad to hear it, it's been a bitch finding anyone willing to venture outside with the trouble we've been having. Why don't you come have a seat and we'll figure out the details. I'm Ursala by the way."
</text>
	<image>village.jpg</image>
	<var>
		<name>questMerchantPassage</name>
		<value>started</value>
	</var>
	<link>
		<file>MerchantHouseInside.xml</file>
		<text>You follow her into the house</text>
	</link>
</tile>