<tile>
	<text>The first thing the wizard does upon entering his dwelling is collect an enormous stack of books and set them in front of you. Upon learning you can't read the large stack is replaced by a much smaller stack of primers. In the seldom experienced moments when you have a reprieve from your work, you wonder if anyone has ever learned to read in less time. However you can't complain, he works harder than you do at stuffing every word ever imagined into your head, and still finds the time and energy to do complicated looking things involving cauldrons and books and staffs and runes and so on. Under his tutelage it is not long before you are reading voraciously, you are halfway through his original assignment before you even realize it. Although it is mainly theory to begin with, it does not take long before you are mastering simple spells. It seems simple to you, but Aeternus seems amazed you are able to summon a light after keep it lit after mere months of training, and your progress seems to be exponential. 

With the basics mastered your time is largely your own now, to learn the subjects which interest you at your own pace. Aeternus leaves for days at a time, sometimes wandering near his home attempting to restore a semblance of balance to the swamp, other times he is gone for much longer. When you ask him of these visits he is tight-lipped, merely stating that he was exploring the world. While you are never bored of experimenting with your new talent, after several months of this pattern, you begin to long for a conversation again. After pouring over his map collection, you decide you could easily make it to Javern and back in the duration of one of the wizard's longer trips, with several days to spare. You resolve to go see Ursala the next time Aeternus leaves. Sure enough, the opportunity presents itself quickly, by the time the sun has begin to sink in the sky you are already to the edge of the swamp. You keep a steady pace for most of the afternoon, until some familiar debris on the side of the rode stops you dead in your tracks. It looks like Ursala's wagon overturned on its side.</text>
	<image>lightswamp.jpg</image>
	<link>
		<file>FindUrsala.xml</file>
		<text>Examine the scene</text>
	</link>
</tile>