<tile>
	<text>She presses into you with the same intensity and passion which impressed you so much on your travels. It is not long before the two of you are sharing more than just a money ledger. With your business thriving, it is only logical to buy a house together in Javern from which to conduct your trading. It seems the two of you were made for each other, each pushing the other to succeed. With her your life is never boring, and your combined skills make your once small business grow quickly, wealth seems to come easily with the two of you so engaged in your work. Your life seems to unfold in an almost predetermined manner. There are still setbacks and struggles, but they never seem more than superficial. There is some talk of children, but in the end neither of you really wants to share the other. Years turn into decades, your modest wealth becomes a fortune, the house becomes a countryside manor, your business an effortless income, sent to you by a small group of trusted managers. You can't imagine a happier life, although not everyone is so lucky. As the years go on tales begin to reach you of conflict stemming from the northeast. Trade becomes more difficult with each passing year, armies become a common occurrence on the roads, and just as dangerous as the bandits they pushed out. When Javern falls for the first time, you and Ursala are already merely names on a tombstone, remembered only for the business which carries your names. As the years pass and wars spread across the land, that too is forgotten. Much much later, the wars have given way to small skirmishes, tired affairs undertaken by a defeated remnant of the once proud people who inhabited these lands. A man in a flowing cloak stands over the faded stone. His face is lined with a sadness and exhaustion that is seldom seen in humans. With an abrupt motion he brings his staff up, then down again, shattering it in two on his knee. He stares for a moment longer, then casts down the useless shards and walks away without looking back.</text>
	<image>towers.jpg</image>
</tile>